<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dstoiko personal blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on dstoiko personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Pong with Go and WebAssembly</title>
      <link>/posts/go-pong-wasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/go-pong-wasm/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR For those of you in a hurry: I made a version of the classic Pong game using Go and WebAssembly. I then embedded that game on my website. Warning: it works only on desktop now (no handling of touch). Here is the game, enjoy:
  Why WebAssembly WebAssembly is a relatively new standard on web browsers. From the Wikipedia page:
 The main goal of WebAssembly is to enable high-performance applications on web pages, but the format is designed to be executed and integrated in other environments as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moona: Part II - HAX</title>
      <link>/posts/moona-2-hax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/moona-2-hax/</guid>
      <description>This is the second article from a series on the story of Moona. Check out the other ones here Moona: Start-up Story Series.
HAX Before flying to Shenzhen, actually as soon as we got accepted into the program, I watched a documentary that had been released by Wired just a few months before. It was starring Bunnie Huang, a brilliant electronics engineer who, while still a grad student at MIT, became the first person to hack the Xbox firmware back in December 2001.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moona: Part I - CES</title>
      <link>/posts/moona-1-ces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/moona-1-ces/</guid>
      <description>This is the first article from a series on the story of Moona. Check out the other ones here Moona: Start-up Story Series.
La French Tech I joined Moona around the time we were selected to take part in the Consumer Electronics Show (CES). My co-founder Coline had taken part in a French start-up contest organized by La French Tech, the French label / movement to promote technology start-ups in France and abroad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moona: Start-up Story Series</title>
      <link>/posts/moona-0-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/moona-0-series/</guid>
      <description>Why Moona Before joining the Moona adventure, I was working on another start-up project, and doing part-time work as a freelance software developer.
I met my co-founder and CEO of Moona, Coline, in 2016. While she was looking for a co-founder after working on the project for a few months already, we were hanging out in the same entrepreneurship circles in Paris and we finally met to start working together informally in November 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post I write in a while&amp;hellip; I had started writing a personal blog around 3 years ago. I wrote a couple of articles at the end of 2016 in order to showcase some data analysis, visualization and code work I&amp;rsquo;d done, then left it aside for quite a while as I was starting to work full-time on Moona and things were getting very busy. A lot of things have happened since then and I want to put some stories and thoughts into writing for whoever might find it interesting or helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My personal blog I&amp;rsquo;m David Stoikovitch. I&amp;rsquo;m a geek entrepreneur with business and data science education, who enjoys learning, tech and building stuff. I previously worked as a freelance software developer and since 2017 I&amp;rsquo;m co-founder and CTO of Moona, a sleep technology company with the vision to improve the sleep of millions of people worldwide.
In this blog you will find:
 Blog posts about hardware and software development, and other tech things Random thoughts (maybe) A showcase of personal projects  You can find me on:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/pong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pong/</guid>
      <description>window.addEventListener(&#34;DOMContentLoaded&#34;, async () = { const go = new Go(); const url = &#34;/pong/main.wasm.gz&#34;; const pako = window.pako; let wasm = pako.ungzip(await (await fetch(url)).arrayBuffer()); // A fetched response might be decompressed twice on Firefox. // See https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=610679 if (wasm[0] === 0x1f &amp;&amp; wasm[1] === 0x8b) { wasm = pako.ungzip(wasm); } const result = await WebAssembly.instantiate(wasm, go.importObject) .catch((err) = { console.error(err); }); document.getElementById(&#34;loading&#34;).remove(); go.run(result.instance); });  Loading.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>