<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dstoiko personal blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on dstoiko personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moona: Part II - HAX</title>
      <link>/posts/moona-2-hax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/moona-2-hax/</guid>
      <description>This is the second article from a series on the story of Moona. Check out the other ones here Moona: Start-up Story Series.
HAX Before flying to Shenzhen, actually as soon as we got accepted into the program, I watched a documentary that had been released by Wired just a few months before. It was starring Bunnie Huang, a brilliant electronics engineer who, while still a grad student at MIT, became the first person to hack the Xbox firmware back in December 2001.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moona: Start-up Story Series</title>
      <link>/posts/moona-0-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/moona-0-series/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing a series of posts about the story of Moona, the start-up company I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on since November 2016.
I will tell the story of our company, our challenges, our mission and how we got from an initial prototype to a shipped product, from the moment I joined, which was 6 months after the project creation, up until now, 3 years later.
This series will include 7 articles after this one, with a focus on product development and technical challenges specific to the hardware-software mix of our venture, but also on team creation and management:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moona: Part I - CES</title>
      <link>/posts/moona-1-ces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/moona-1-ces/</guid>
      <description> Going to CES </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post I write in a while&amp;hellip; I had started writing a personal blog around 3 years ago. I wrote a couple of articles at the end of 2016 in order to showcase some data analysis, visualization and code work I&amp;rsquo;d done, then left it aside for quite a while as I was starting to work full-time on Moona and things were getting very busy. A lot of things have happened since then and I want to put some stories and thoughts into writing for whoever might find it interesting or helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description> My personal blog In this blog you will find:
 Blog posts about hardware and software development, product management and other stuff Random thoughts (maybe) A showcase of personal projects  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>